hey guys rexin here welcome to another
crash course guide this time for D and I
will get straight into her rotation so
for her for gauge there's three parts to
it each part is 30 points so up to 90
points and her basic attack chain has
only three combos so 1 2 3 and
completing a full combo will give her 45
points to her forte so 45 out of 90
that's half gauge and Performing intro
attack will also give another 45 points
and once you have full gauge all you
need to do is press her resonance skill
I'll call it e over here all you do is e
basic e e e 3 e after that so like this
e basic e e e and that's it
congratulations you've already mastered
so now we'll talk a bit more on how her
forte actually works so her e skill will
only be enhanced if she has at least two
gauges so 60 points and then she'll
convert it to the mark on the left and
on the right as you saw earlier in the
footage and you can also place them in
mid a if you press and hold e instead so
I'm just going to do it right now press
and hold
e and there we go and now all you need
to do is press e to teleport to any of
the marks you can also face them if you
want if you want to specifically
teleport to them like this and like this
and there you go so 60 gauge to place
left and right and then there's one one
more Mark which is the middle Mark
through five different types of trigger
however the easiest one is still
pressing basic right after e with a full
gauge like the initial rotation I showed
you otherwise you can also just do jump
and heavy and there we go we've already
span one gauge that's the middle
one so for demonstration I'm just going
to press and hold e to place them in the
air and then press basic right after
that since I have a full gauge to place
the middle one so like this press and
hold e press
basic there you go and then I have three
marks now left right and middle so just
press e on any of
them like that and she'll automatically
attack them so ideally you want to do
the three marks version because it has
the most damage like after the third e
she gets bonus damage out of it like
bonus hits out of it try to do the full
set so we can also do it this way I have
two gauges here so that's already enough
for my e left and right Mark like
that and then I'll just spend the third
one for the mark this heavy air heavy
that's good enough e e e like that you
can also time your e if you want to be
strategic with your
Dodges like that two gauges again three
gauges e
basic e e e like that pretty fun as for
her residence Liberation it's similar to
Mori so once she does her ultimate you
get coordinated attacks even even when
she's off screen or you can also keep
her on screen so I'll do it like right
now and you'll see there we go those are
the attacks so these attacks will also
fill up Jin's gauge really quickly
coordinated attacks just like that
switch her
out so it's still
ongoing so the whole Liberation lasts
for 30 seconds or after 21 coordinated
attacks are complete pretty good so
that's about it for Z's uh Forte it's
pretty simple all you need to do you
don't have to think so much is once she
has a three gauge just press e basic e e
e so three
gauge e basic e e e that's
it there's obviously more nuances to
this so you can read the rest in her
tool tips this is just the basics so e
basic e e e e that's it one other thing
to note is that her air Dodge is always
reset every time she does the air e like
this so I'm going to E I can dodge like
that E I can dodge again so pretty good
as for her outro skill it's glacial buff
and also resonance skill amplify 25% for
14 seconds for the next character that's
why she's extremely good for jiny as for
inherent skill the first one increases
attack by 6% up to three stacks after
she uses stroke of Genius or creation
Zenith that's the one where she uses uh
E when she teleports into her Mark and
for her second inherent skill this is
the good one this is similar to yyang
where she gives more ultimate charge to
the next character so she's two in one
basically yangyang's uh outro skill plus
glacial plus resonance buff as for her
weapon obviously the weapon that comes
with her Banner is her best weapon rhyme
drain sprouts with a really high CR
damage at 72% at level 90 and it
increases attack by 12% and using
resonance skill grunts up to three
stacks of basic attack bonus of 12% so
up to 36% for 6 seconds and after three
stacks you can safely switch her out
with her outro skill and it'll buff
herself with 52% basic attack damage
bonus so this will be really good when
you use her resonance Liberation
coordinated attack and then you switch
her out and it's going to be massively
buffed and if you don't have a weapon
yinin string Master also works for star
followed by Cosmic Ripples and if you
don't have either of those variation or
any other fourstar weapon works for her
as well pretty straightforward when it
comes to skill leveling priority
basically always go for the two inherent
skills and also Forte circuit and
resonance Liberation just prioritize
these two and the two inherent skills
and then you can do up the rest later on
resonance skill normal attack and intro
skill as for her Echo moonlit set is
good on her you can just go 44111
configuration so two bosses and three
one cost Echoes all on attack main stat
and for the two four cost Echoes you can
just go crit crit rate and crit damage
usually your healer will be using the
turtle main Echo so you can set
impermanence Heron as her main Echo so
that she will buff the third character
and for her energy regen getting about
130% is already good enough for her to
get her Ultimate Off consistently of
course if you want to play her as a main
DPS especially if you have a festar
weapon you can also go glacial set 43311
glacial set that is all also fine now
for her resonance chain it's mostly
damage increase for herself I would say
s0 is already good enough to play uh D
normally S1 gives her even more
resonance energy when she uses creation
Zenith so creation Zenith is is a skill
where she does e three times so only on
full gauge that's the one called
creation Zenith and she gets resonance
energy restored by 15 and crit rate
increased by 10% for the rest it's just
more damage and for the fourth chain
it's attack increased by % this is the
generic one for everybody when she does
her resonance Liberation and beyond that
it's just more and more damage if you're
a big fan of her you can consider going
all the way otherwise S zero is good
enough as for team composition we've
already discussed before so Verina the
overwork Verina will always be in a team
for every team composition followed BYU
to buff jiny this is the highly
recommended team however since JSU also
gives energy charge to the next
character she's pretty versatile you can
put anybody here for fast Master energy
gain you can even put changli as well
and if you really want zudu to be the
main damage dealer in your team you can
also put sanwa here and she'll buff her
basic attack because Dudu is all about
basic attack you can set this team up as
well as I said before she's pretty
versatile you can place her as the third
character main DPS and hold glacial set
or most of the time she's going to be
the second character holding the moonlit
Echo set to buff the third character and
that's pretty much it for the crash
course for J hopefully this crash course
guide has helped you in understanding
more about J's play style and how to
build her consider leaving a like
comment and subscribe to the channel and
I'll see you in the next video bye-bye